The answer to this question is a bit surprising or at least,
إجابة هذا السؤال مفاجئة بعض الشيء أو أنني
it surprised me when I first learned it.
.قد تفاجأت على الأقل عند معرفتي بها لأول مرة
Because Numpy arrays have different behavior than Python lists.
نظرًا لأن صفائف Numpy .لها سلوك مختلف مقارنة بقوائم Python
You start off with the variable a referring to the array 1, 2, 3, 4, 5.
ستبدأ بالمتغير .aبالإشارة إلى الصفيف 1 و 2 و 3 و 4 و 5
However, when you take a slice of the first three elements of the array a,
ومع ذلك، عندما تستخدم جزءًا من ،العناصر الثلاثة الأولى من الصفيف a
Numpy doesn't actually create a new array.
فلن يُنشئ صفيف Numpy .صفيفًا جديدًا
Instead, slice refers to what's called a view of the original array.
وبدلاً من ذلك، يشير الجزء إلى .ما يُسمى عرض الصفيف الأصلي
It will look like a new array, but
،سيبدو الصفيف الأصلي كصفيف جديد
if you modify it, the original array is modified as well.
،ولكن إذا قمت بتعديله .سيتم تعديل الصفيف الأصلي أيضًا
This makes slicing a Numpy very fast,
،وهذا يسرع تقسيم صفائف Numpy جدًا
since you don't have to create a new array or copy any new values.
لأنك لا تحتاج إلى إنشاء .صفيف جديد أو نسخ أي قيم جديدة
But it means you should be very careful any time you want to modify
ولكن هذا يعني أنه عليك أن تكون حريصًا جدًا في أي وقت ترغب فيه بتعديل
a slice of an array.
.جزء من صفيف ما
So the correct answer here is that the output is this second choice.
وهذا يعني أن .الإجابة الصحيحة هي أن الإخراج هو هذا الخيار الثاني
An array containing 100, 2, 3, 4, and 5.
.أي صفيف يحتوي على 100 و 2 و3 و4 و5